A Guide to the Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection, 1998-2008
Thomas Balch Library
Thomas Balch Library
Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection 1998-2008
Thomas Balch Library
VC RG20
The Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection is arranged in two series. Series 1 contains primarily aerial photographic prints of Leesburg from 2000-2008. Series 2 consists of special event and ribbon cutting ceremony photographic prints in downtown Leesburg from 1998-2005.
Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection open for research.
Acquisition Information
Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development and Tourism
Alternative Form Available
Digital surrogates for some items
Accruals
2001.0008, 2007.0130, 2008.0026, 2009.0021, 2010.0246
Historical Information
Economic Development was directed by Executive Department from 1991 to 1997. The Department of Economic Development was established by Leesburg Town Council in Fiscal Year 1998 "to position Leesburg for positive economic growth through commercial, industrial, residential, cultural and social development." In 2004, the Department's duties were expanded to assist in fostering tourism. In Fiscal Year 2008, the Department became the Economic Development and Tourism Division of the Executive Department.
Scope and Content
The Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection is arranged in two series. Series 1 contains primarily aerial photographic prints of Leesburg from 2000-2008. Series 2 consists of special event and ribbon cutting ceremony photographic prints in downtown Leesburg from 1998-2005.
Series 1, which comprises the bulk of the collection, contains 4"x6" photographic prints, primarily aerial and many with digital surrogates or negative. Long-time Leesburg resident and insurance agent Sam Legard was hired by the Town to take the photographs. They capture residential and commercial growth in Leesburg and the immediately surrounding areas, especially to the east. Shopping centers at Fort Evans Road, Edwards Ferry Road, and the Leesburg Bypass, as well as commercial and residential development around Battlefield Parkway figure prominently. In the northern end of Leesburg, expansion at Ida Lee Park and Loudoun Hospital, renovations at Morven Park, and the addition of a public school complex are visually recorded.
Series 2 consists of special event and ribbon cutting ceremony photographs collected by the Department of Economic Development. Included are ceremonies for the Leesburg Vintner and the Leesburg Bookstore, then-governor Mark Warner's rally in Leesburg in 2005, and Fall into the Arts in 2006.
Original digital images exist after the latter part of 2006. Images are catalogued in PastPerfect, Thomas Balch Library's visual collections database available onsite, in groups that represent specific sites of interest or rolls of film. The images may be identified in the online index available at www.leesburgva.gov/ThomasBalchLibrary/SpecialCollections by searching vc_rg20.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Town of Leesburg, Department of Economic Development Photograph Collection 1998-2008 (VC RG20), Thomas Balch Library, Leesburg, VA.
Other Finding Aid
Past Perfect Catalogue records
Technical Requirements
Electronic Media
Related Material
Town of Leesburg Records, RG20 (Department of Economic Development)
Contents List
- (SERIES 1: Aerial Photographs)
  - 1
    - 2-6-2000 Leesburg, VA [folder record: 19 photos], 02/06/2000 02/06/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 2-6-2000 [folder record: 4 photos], >02/06/2000
    - [ca. 25 February 2000, folder record: 3 photos], 02/25/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 2-25-2000 [folder record: 22 photos], 02/25/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 3-10-2000 [folder record: 19 photos], 03/10/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 3-18-2000 [folder record: 21 photos], 03/18/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 3-30-2000 [folder record: 7 photos], 03/30/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 4-7-2000 [folder record: 16 photos], 04/07/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 4-24-2000 [folder record: 10 photos], 04/24/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 5-17-2000 [folder record: 21 photos], 05/17/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 5-26-2000 [folder record: 24 photos], 05/26/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 8-8-2000 [folder record: 3 photos], 08/08/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 8-8-2000 [folder record: 20 photos], 08/08/2000
  - 2
    - [ca. 8 August 2000, folder record: 4 photos], 08/08/2000
    - 8-10-2000 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 8 photos], 08/10/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 8-12-2000 [folder entry: 4 photos], 08/12/2000
    - 8-26-2000 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 8 photos], 08/26/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 9-6-2000 [folder entry: 8 photos], 09/06/2000
    - [ca. 20 September 2000, folder entry: 4 photos], 09/20/2000
    - 9-30-2000 [folder entry: 4 photos], 09/30/2000
    - 11-2-2000 [folder entry: 19 photos], 11/02/2000
    - 11-2-2000 [folder entry: 10 photos], 11/02/2000
    - Leesburg, VA 1-23-2001 [folder entry: 15 photos], 01/23/2001
    - [ca. 24 January 2001, folder entry: 8 photos], 01/24/2001
    - 2-23-2001 [folder entry: 14 photos], 02/23/2001
    - Leesburg, VA 3-3-2001 [folder entry: 24 photos], 03/03/2001
    - 3-8-2001 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 8 photos], 03/08/2001
    - 3-8-2001 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 12 photos], 03/08/2001
    - 3-17-2001 [folder entry: 4 photos], 03/17/2001
    - Leesburg, VA 3-19-2001 [folder entry: 12 photos], 03/19/2001
    - 3-19-2001 Leesburg, VA Air [folder entry: 8 photos], 03/19/2001
    - [[ca. 20 March 2001, folder entry: 4 photos], 03/20/2001
  - 3
    - Air - Leesburg, VA 4-4-2001 [folder entry: 4 photos], 04/04/2001
    - 4-18-2001 [folder entry: 28 photos], 04/18/2001
    - 4-18-2001 [folder entry: 21 photos], 04/18/2001
    - [ca. 23 April 2001; folder entry: 4 photos], 04/23/2001
    - 24 New Hangers [sic] Row 2-3 toward East, Leesburg Airport Oct 2001 [sic, photos developed 13 June 2001; folder entry: 4 photos], 06/13/2001
    - 11-24-2001 Leesburg, VA Air [folder entry: 5 photos], 11/24/2001
    - 12-19-2001 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 20 photos], 12/19/2001
    - 12-19-2001 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 4 photos], 12/19/2001
    - 12-21-2001 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 4 photos], 12/21/2001
    - Leesburg, VA 2-19-2002 [106M, folder entry: 21 photos], 02/19/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 2-19-2002 [107M, folder entry: 12 photos], 02/19/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 2-19-2002 [112M, folder entry: 21 photos], 02/19/2002
    - [19 February 2002, folder entry: 3 photos], 02/19/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 2-23-2002 [folder entry: 11 photos], 02/23/2002
    - Old Hanger [sic], Leesburg Airport 3-9-2002 [folder entry: 11 photos], 03/09/2002
    - 6-22-2002, Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 12 photos], 06/22/2002
  - 4
    - 6-22-2002, Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 12 photos], 06/22/2002
    - [22 June & 11 July 2002; folder entry: 2 photos], 06/22/2002
    - 7-30-2002 Leesburg, VA Air [folder entry: 12 photos], 07/30/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 9-5-2002 [folder entry: 4 photos], 09/05/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 9-6-2002 [folder entry: 2 photos], 09/06/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 9-6-2002 [folder entry: 24 photos], 09/06/2002
    - 9-25-2002 [folder entry: 20 photos], 09/25/2002
    - Leesburg, VA 9-25-2002 [folder entry: 24 photos], 09/25/2002
    - 11-9-2002 [folder entry: 14 photos], 11/09/2002
    - 11-14-2002 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 7 photos], 11/14/2002
    - 1-16-2003 [folder entry: 12 photos], 01/16/2003
    - Leesburg, VA Airport [folder entry: 6 photos], 02/18/2003
    - Airport/Leesburg 2-20-2003 [folder entry: 5 photos], 02/20/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 4-30-2003 [folder entry: 18 photos], 04/30/2003
    - 5-14-2003 [folder entry: 16 photos], 05/14/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 6-28-2003 [roll 006096, folder entry: 22 photos], 06/28/2003
  - 5
    - [28 June 2003, roll 006097; folder entry: 16 photos], 06/28/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 6-28-2003 [folder entry: 27 photos], 06/28/2003
    - 7-25-2003 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 2 photos], 07/25/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 7-30-2003 [folder entry: 10 photos], 07/30/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 8-10-2003 [folder entry: 14 photos], 08/10/2003
    - [12 August 2003; folder entry: 2 photos], 08/12/2003
    - 8-19-2003 Leesburg, VA [roll 001379, folder entry: 12 photos], 08/19/2003
    - 8-19-2003 Leesburg, VA [roll 001380, folder entry: 20 photos], 08/19/2003
    - 9-16-2003 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 16 photos], 09/16/2003
    - 9-16-2003 Leesburg, VA [roll 003882; folder entry: 10 photos], 09/16/2003
    - Leesburg, VA 10-28-2003 [folder entry: 12 photos], 10/28/2003
    - 10-30-2003 [folder entry: 12 photos], 10/30/2003
    - 10-30-2003 Leesburg, VA [roll 007681; folder entry: 20 photos], 10/30/2003
    - 11-21-2003 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 25 photos], 11/21/2003
    - 1-14-2004 Leesburg, VA [roll 005812; folder entry: 23 photos], 01/14/2004
  - 6
    - Leesburg, VA Jan. 14, 2004 [roll 0058170; folder entry: 8 photos], 01/14/2004
    - 1-14-2004 Leesburg, VA [roll 005818, folder entry: 6 photos], 01/14/2004
    - Jan. 14 2004 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos], 01/14/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 3-18-2004 [roll 000323; folder entry: 22 photos], 03/18/2004
    - Leesburg, VA Air 3-18-2004 [roll 000324; folder entry: 24 photos], 03/18/2004
    - 3-18-2004 Leesburg, VA [roll 000326; folder entry: 24 photos], 03/18/2004
    - [18 March 2004, new Giant; folder entry: 4 photos], 03/18/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 4-6-2004 [roll 001579; folder entry: 21 photos], 04/06/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 4-6-2004 [roll 001581; folder entry: 15 photos], 04/06/2004
    - 4-6-2004 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 10 photos], 04/06/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 4-24-2004 [roll 003156; folder entry: 24 photos], 04/24/2004
    - 4-24-2004 [roll 003157; folder entry: 23 photos], 04/24/2004
    - 6-12-2004 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 14 photos], 06/12/2004
    - 6-12-2004 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 12 photos], 06/12/2004
    - 6-12-2004 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 10 photos], 06/12/2004
  - 7
    - Leesburg, VA 6-29-2004 [folder entry: 11 photos], 06/29/2004
    - [29 June 2004; folder entry: 4 photos], 06/29/2004
    - Barber & Ross 7-29-2004 [folder entry: 7 photos], 07/29/2004
    - Leesburg, VA Aug-19-2004 [roll 003817; folder entry: 24 photos], 08/14/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 8-19-2004 [roll 003818; folder entry: 32 photos], 08/19/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 8-19-2004 [roll 003819; folder entry: 6 photos], 08/19/2004
    - Leesburg, VA Aug-19-2004 [roll 003820; folder entry: 14 photos], 08/19/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 8-22-2004 [roll 000179; folder entry: 12 photos], 08/22/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 8-22-2004 [roll 000180; folder entry: 19 photos], 08/22/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 8-22-2004 [roll 000182; folder entry: 24 photos], 08/22/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 9-2-2004 [roll 001122; folder entry: 16 photos], 09/02/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 10-27-2004 [folder entry: 12 photos], 10/27/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 10-27-2004 [folder entry: 4 photos], 10/27/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 11-2-2004 [roll 006355; folder entry: 18 photos], 11/02/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 11-6-2004 [roll 006853; folder entry: 18 photos], 11/06/2004
    - 11-11-2004 [folder entry: 4 photos], 11/11/2004
  - 8
    - Leesburg, VA 11-26-2004 [roll 008624; folder entry: 24 photos], 11/26/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 11-26-2004 [roll 008626; folder entry: 17 photos], 11/26/2004
    - [26 November 2004; folder entry: 3 photos], 11/26/2004
    - Leesburg, VA 12-10-2004 [folder entry: 12 photos], 12/10/2004
    - Leesburg, VA Dec 28-2004 [folder entry: 20 photos], 12/28/2004
    - [28 December 2004; folder entry: 14 photos], 12/28/2004
    - Leesburg, VA Jan 27, 2005 [roll 003565; folder entry: 25 photos], 01/27/2005
    - Jan 27, 2005 [roll 003567; folder entry: 33 photos], 01/27/2005
    - 2-22-2005 Leesburg, VA [roll 005292; folder entry: 24 photos], 02/22/2005
    - [22 February 2005, roll 005293; folder entry: 8 photos], 02/22/2005
    - 2-22-2005 Leesburg, VA [roll 005316; folder entry: 26 photos], 02/22/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 3-22-2005 [roll 006922; folder entry: 25 photos], 03/22/2005
  - 9
    - Leesburg, VA 3-22-2005 [roll 006924; folder entry: 18 photos], 03/22/2005
    - Leesburg, VA Next to Airport, June 21, 2005 [roll 002260; folder entry: 23 photos], 06/21/2005
    - Leesburg, VA June 21, 2005 [roll 002401; folder entry: 12 photos], 06/21/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 6-21-2005 [roll 002408; folder entry: 20 photos], 06/21/2005
    - [17 August 2005, roll 005939; folder entry: 2 photos], 08/17/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 8-17-2005 [roll 005941; folder entry: 23 photos], 08/17/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 8-31-2005 [folder entry: 8 photos], 08/31/2005
    - [2 September 2005; folder entry: 7 photos], 09/02/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 9-2-2005 [folder entry: 29 photos], 09/02/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 9-2-2005 [folder entry: 16 photos; includes negatives], 09/02/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 10-30-2005 [009876; folder entry: 8 photos], 10/30/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 10-30-2005 [folder entry: 12 photos], 10/30/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 10-30-2005 [folder entry: 19 photos], 10/30/2005
    - Leesburg, VA 11-4-2005 1800' high [000156; folder entry: 32 photos], 11/04/2005
    - [4 November 2005, 000157; folder entry: 8 photos], 11/04/2005
  - 10
    - 1-30-2006 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 8 photos], 01/30/2006
    - 1-30-2006 Leesburg VA 2006 [folder entry: 6 photos], 01/30/2006
    - [30 January 2006; folder entry: 4 photos], 01/30/2006
    - Jan 30 2006 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 34 photos], 01/30/2006
    - [7 March 2006; folder entry: 32 photos], 03/07/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 3-7-2006 [folder entry: 22 photos], 03/07/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 4-29-2006 [folder entry: 23 photos], 04/29/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 4-29-2006 [folder entry: 24 photos], 04/29/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 4-29-2006 [folder entry: 20 photos], 04/29/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 6-5-2006 [folder entry: 10 photos], 06/05/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 6-5-2006 [folder entry: 25 photos], 06/05/2006
  - 11
    - Leesburg, VA 6-5-2006 [folder entry: 23 photos], 06/05/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 6-5-2006 [folder entry: 11 photos], 06/05/2006
    - #1 6-16-2006 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos], 06/16/2006
    - #2 6-16-2006 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos], 06/16/2006
    - 6-22-2006 Leesburg, VA Crosstrails [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 001715], 06/22/2006
    - 6-22-2006 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 12 photos], 06/22/2006
    - 7-24-2006 Leesburg, VA #1 [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 003079/003080/003081], 07/24/2006
    - 7-24-2006 Leesburg, VA #2 [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 003079/003080/003081], 07/24/2006
  - 12
    - 7-24-2006 Leesburg, VA #3 [folder entry: 23 photos; combo CD 003079/003080/003081], 07/24/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-5-2006 #1 [folder entry: 23 photos; combo CD 003743/003744/003745], 08/05/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-5-2006 #2 [folder entry: 23 photos; combo CD 003743/003744/003745], 08/05/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-5-2006 #3 [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 003743/003744/003745], 08/05/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-11-2006 #1 [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 004025/004026], 08/11/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-11-2006 #2 [folder entry: 23 photos; combo CD 004025/004026], 08/11/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-17-2006 [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 004393], 08/17/2006
    - [17 September 2006; folder entry: 20 photos; combo CD 005564/005565/005566], 09/17/2006
    - 9-17-2006 Leesburg, VA #2 [folder entry: 23 photos; combo CD 005564/005565/005566], 09/17/2006
  - 13
    - 9-17-2006 Leesburg, VA #3 [folder entry: 22 photos; combo CD 005564/005565/005566], 09/17/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 10-9-2006 #1 [folder entry: 14 photos; combo CD 006336/006337], 10/09/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 10-9-2006 #2 [folder entry: 22 photos; combo CD 006336/006337], 10/09/2006
    - Lansdowne 10-9-2006 [folder entry: 20 photos], 10/09/2006
    - 10-31-2006 Leesburg, VA 1 [folder entry: 20 photos; combo CD 007144/007145/007146], 10/31/2006
    - 10-31-2006 Leesburg, VA #2 [folder entry: 21 photos; combo CD 007144/007145/007146], 10/31/2006
    - 10-31-2006 Leesburg, VA #3 [folder entry: 20 photos; combo CD 007144/007145/007146], 10/31/2006
    - 11-10-2006 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos], 11/10/2006
    - 12-20-2006 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 009947/009948], 12/20/2006
  - 14
    - 12-20-2006 Leesburg, VA #2 [folder entry: 24 photos; combo CD 009947/009948], 12/20/2006
    - Leesburg, VA Jan 27 2007 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 001466], 01/27/2007
    - [27 Jan 2007, folder entry: 5 photos; CD 001464], 01/27/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 3-7-2007 [folder entry: 3 photos], 03/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 3-9-2007 [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 002498], 03/09/2007
    - 3-9-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 2496], 03/09/2007
    - 3-9-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2497], 03/09/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 4-20-2007 [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 009835], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Battlefield Parkway 4-20-2007 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 009831], 04/20/2007
  - 15
    - Leesburg, VA 4-20-2007 [folder entry: 24 photos], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Hospital 4-20-2007 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 009834], 04/20/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-7-2007 [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 00035927], 05/07/2007
    - 5-7-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 30 photos; CD 001264], 05/07/2007
    - Leesburg, VA 5-7-2007 Battlefield Parkway Town [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 00035929], 05/07/2007
    - 5-19-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 37 photos; CD 002496], 05/19/2007
    - 5-19-2007 Leesburg, VA Battlefield Parkway [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 002497], 05/19/2007
    - 5-19-2007 Leesburg, VA The Circle [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 002495], 05/19/2007
  - 16
    - 6-7-2007 Leesburg, VA Carr Area [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 003770], 06/07/2007
    - 6-7-2007 Leesburg, VA Cornwall Site [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 003754], 06/07/2007
    - 6-7-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 003748], 06/07/2007
    - 6-21-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 004809], 06/21/2007
    - 6-21-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 004808], 06/21/2007
    - 6-21-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 004807], 06/21/2007
    - 6-21-2007 Cornwall Pavillion Site Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 004811], 06/21/2007
    - 7-2-2007 Landsdown [sic] Area - Shopping Center - Hospital [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 005730], 07/02/2007
    - Leesburg, VA Cornwall Pavillion 7-2-2007 [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 005731], 07/02/2007
  - 17
    - Leesburg, VA 7-2-2007 [folder entry: 18 photos; CD 005732], 07/02/2007
    - 7-2-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 20 photos; CD 005733], 07/02/2007
    - Cornwall Site Leesburg Hospital 7-14-2007 [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 006709], 07/14/2007
    - 7-14-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 006707], 07/14/2007
    - 7-14-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 22 photos; CD 006708], 07/14/2007
    - 7-14-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 20 photos; CD 006705], 07/14/2007
    - 8-10-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 13 photos; CD 009957], 08/10/2007
    - 8-14-2007 Leesburg, VA Goose Creek Area [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 009952], 08/14/2007
    - 8-14-2007 Leesburg, VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 009956], 08/14/2007
  - 18
    - Leesburg Hospital Cornwall Pavillion 8-14-2007 [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 009953], 08/14/2007
    - Leesburg Hospital Cornwall Pavillion LP 8-14-2007 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 009954], 08/14/2007
    - 8-14-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 009963], 08/14/2007
    - 9-3-2007 Leesburg VA Hospital Cook [folder entry: 14 photos; CD 1834-A], 09/03/2007
    - 9-3-2007 Leesburg VA - Battlefield Pk - River Creek & Rt 7 [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 1836-A], 09/03/2007
    - 9-3-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 1835-A], 09/03/2007
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA Hospital [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2954-A], 09/17/2007
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA Downtown #1 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2953-A], 09/19/2007
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA Downtown #2 [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2946-A], 09/19/2007
  - 19
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA Kincaid Farm [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 2952-A], 09/19/2007
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos], 09/19/2007
    - 9-19-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2947-A], 09/19/2007
    - 10-14-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 4404-A], 10/14/2007
    - 10-14-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 4410-A], 10/14/2007
    - 10-14-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 18 photos], 10/14/2007
    - 10-19-2007 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 6 photos], 10/19/2007
    - Air Photos Inova Hospital 3-17-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 3883-A], 03/17/2008
    - 3-17-2008 Air Photos Leesburg VA [folder entry: 25 photos; CD 3884-A], 03/17/2008
    - 3-17-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 2 photos; CD 3886-A], 03/17/2008
    - Air Photos 3-17-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 3885-A], 03/17/2008
  - 20
    - 6-12-2008 #1 Rt 7 & Rivercreek Interchange Leesburg VA [folder entry: 4 photos; CD 7895-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #2 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 28 photos; CD 7908-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #3 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 7907-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #4 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 7897-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #5 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 7899-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #6 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 7901-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #7 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 7902-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 #8 Hospital - Rust Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 7904-A], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 Leesburg VA Belmont Area [folder entry: 4 photos], 06/12/2008
    - 6-12-2008 Water Plant Leesburg VA [folder entry: 4 photos], 06/12/2008
    - #1 8-20-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2184-A], 08/20/2008
  - 21
    - #2 8-20-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2187-A], 08/20/2008
    - #3 8-20-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2182-A], 08/20/2008
    - #4 8-20-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 24 photos; CD 2179-A], 08/20/2008
    - #1 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6962-A], 11/07/2008
    - #2 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6967-A], 11/07/2008
    - #3 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6966-A], 11/07/2008
    - #4 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6963-A], 11/07/2008
    - #5 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6964-A], 11/07/2008
    - #6 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6968-A], 11/07/2008
    - #7 11-7-2008 Leesburg VA [folder entry: 23 photos; CD 6965-A], 11/07/2008
- (SERIES 2: Event Photographs)
  - 22
    - [December 1998; folder entry: 14 photos], 12/1998
    - [Fall 2003; folder entry: 1 photos], 06/25/2005
    - [Spring 2005; folder entry: 36 photos & 25 negatives], 05/17/2005
    - Fall into the Arts 06 [folder entry: 21 photos & 24 negatives], 09/2006
  - 1
    - Crosstrails 6-22-2006 Leesburg, VA [CD 001715], 06/22/2006
    - 7-24-2006 [3 rolls, combo CD 003079/003080/003081], 07/24/2006
    - Air Photo's Leesburg, VA 8-5-2006 [3 rolls, combo CD 003743/003744/003745], 08/05/2006
    - 8-11-2006 [2 rolls, combo CD 004025/004026], 08/11/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 8-17-2006 [CD 004393], 08/17/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 9-17-2006 [3 rolls, combo CD 005564/005565/005566], 09/17/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 10-9-2006 #1/Leesburg, VA 10-9-2006 #1 [2 rolls, combo CD 006336/006337], 10/09/2006
    - Leesburg, VA 10-31-2006 #1/ Leesburg, VA 10-31-2006 #2/ Leesburg, VA 10-31-2006 #3 [3 rolls, combo CD 007144/007145/007146], 10/31/2006
    - 12-20-2006 Leesburg, VA #1/12-20-2006 Leesburg, VA #2 [2 rolls, combo CD 009947/009948], 12/20/2006
    - Leesburg & Hospital 1-27-2007 [CD 001466], 01/27/2007
    - Landsdown [sic] - Hospital 1-27-2007 [CD 001464], 01/27/2007
    - March 9 2009 [CD 002498], 03/09/2009